He's the reason why
Company.
Hundreds will die.
and we have to fight together.
Let's go. C'mon C'mon.
even to the gods.
Gentlemen, please.
To my right.
You too, come on.
C'mon C'mon.
take Winterfell, my lady.
Ramsay Bolton cannot
How many men were
necessary to face it?
from Bear Island...
The shame was so heavy
It was a woman.
I think some people
they are afraid of you.
I'm used to it.
we are cowards.
who had been dead for days.
It was smelly,
with animals everywhere...
and bones coming out of here.
You are an anointed knight.
that the war is not between
I almost died of fright.
No need to ask
I put it in the cart, but it didn't happen.
I thought I would die
on other days, but no.
What made him live?
But you must go, grandma.
- Lord Edmure.
It's still here for a reason.
Yes there is. I'm hard to kill.
We will go to Meereen.
The gods still
They want you here.
I've heard this before.
- as a wife.
of another god.
Our two old houses
I don't know much about the gods.
You are not in the right career.
There are many godly motherfuckers
Who do they think they know...
the word of god or gods.
It's not me. I don't even know the name
truth about them.
Maybe it's the Seven.
most experienced in Westeros.
It's your brother?
Or maybe everything is
the same thing.
I don't know.
What matters, I believe...
I think I have beer
As long as you are alive,
And whatever it is...
will involve Sandor Clegane.
I didn't know myself before.
You don't know the things I've done.
Stannis as much as the Boltons.
If gods exist...
hundreds of generations.
that the war is not between
Majesty.
What are we going to read today?
- The Mother's Book,
- His Holiness.
Capítulo 3, verso 12.
“The water passes through the stones,
leveling..."
But you must go, grandma.
He's the reason why
Company.
the brute nature of a man.
The wife relieves the injuries
your husband...
the mother sings
for your child to sleep."
You learn fast.
See you soon, dear.
every verse of the holy book...
House Stark for centuries.
of mercy from the Mother...
and wild
who doesn't know how to read...
to understand
the wisdom of the Father.
For years, I...
I pretended to love the poor,
the afflicted.
I felt sorry for them, but...
I never loved them.
They disgusted me.
They are hard to love.
The poor make us sick
Because we are...
without our illusions.
They show us what we would be like
without our fine clothes.
What would we smell like?
without perfume.
I can do
an intimate question?
He is fine.
The king mentioned that,
We must defend them.
of the Immaculate.
in your wedding bed.
No.
I am your killer.
you are women and children.
After they're done with me,
even to the gods.
Let's go. C'mon C'mon.
But we were not animals.
I don't have them anymore.
Congress requires no desire
by the woman...
We have Lord Edmure.
and we need to defeat them
if we want to continue
while your mother screamed
and my friends held her.
Sometimes it's hard to find
the right way.
Hard to find and more
difficult to navigate.
But it has already made a lot of progress.
I pray your grandmother follows you.
My grandmother?
Yes.
The Queen of Thorns
burned like Mance.
a strong woman...
and an unrepentant sinner.
I should teach you
the new path...
as she taught him the old man.
- Or I fear
- for her safety...
Body and soul.
Does she move or talk?
I want to talk to you alone.
Septa Unella is my true one
friend and advisor.
This is crazy!
Not in your sanctuary
He's the reason why
Company.
Hundreds will die.
they will come after you.
Drink it.
- Until you ask them to stop.
If I ask them to stop.
You don't want my ring.
Grandma, stop.
what did they do to you?
You marched against
the High Sparrow, against the Faith.
We march for you.
that we have.
but they showed mercy.
It's your brother?
What mercy did they show him?
Loras' only hope
is to confess and repent.
If you do this, faith will allow
-I've heard enough.
He will have to resign
They thought I was brave.
stand out in memory.
I didn't know myself before.
He is the heir of the Garden
from Above, the future House Tyrell.
-He can start again.
-Like a stupid fanatic.
without perfume.
- Will leave for
- Now I would like
I fought them in Durolar.
this should stay here.
I'm the queen.
It is my duty to serve
my husband, the king.
But you must go, grandma.
Your place is at home.
I will never leave her.
- -Never.
- -You must.
Go home.
Find comfort
Yes, you.
You learn fast.
See you soon, dear.
House Stark for centuries.
She was a great warrior.
We said we would fight
like you...
when the time came,
and we were serious...
but that was not what was agreed.
He was the commander
You lost, Cersei.
Chose this place
no one would be here.
You would all be meat
in the Night King's army.
Regicide.
burned like Mance.
Remember the camp
from Mance? I went to the horizon.
And look at us now.
You are a Westerosi.
If we lose this...
Lost.
If gods exist...
hundreds of generations.
As if we never existed.
We will be the last
of the Free People.
This is what will happen
with you if we lose.
The Boltons, the Karstarks,
the Umbers...
And we will leave at dawn.
He's the reason why
Welcome to Bear Island.
Hundreds will die.
they will come after you.
Drink it.
- Until you ask them to stop.
I don't have them anymore.
Congress requires no desire
We need more men.
We have Lord Edmure.
and we need to defeat them
We are not a big house,
On my honor.
because he said
by the Free People...
when none
Hard to find and more
for a war
- -Hang on.
you will see an army at the gates,
we are cowards.
And if that's what we are...
we deserve to be
the last Free Peoples.
Snow.
Are you sure they will come?
We are not that smart
like you southerners.
When we say
we will do something...
Right, Mr. Davos
on other days, but no.
albeit from King's Landing.
see who I deal with.
Your grandson is still a prisoner.
It's still here for a reason.
rotting in a cell?
Now, let's say I threaten
in a cell because of you.
However, the man spoke
this city because of you.
Our two old houses
of another god.
because of you
and your stupidity.
You are sure.
I made a horrible mistake.
I carry it with me every day.
Great.
Brought an army
of fanatics at our door.
And now we must fight
What mercy did they show him?
We need each other.
- We sent ravens
person I've ever met.
Make your men
It's hard to remember.
But the most perverse
stand out in memory.
- To remember
These are our towers...
When my grandchildren were
dragged to their cells?
And make no mistake, my lady...
If gods exist...
But we still have a chance...
I love my son.
in the Fist of the First Men.
We must defend them.
I'm leaving this town as soon as possible
as soon as possible before...
that that fanatic without shoes
throw me in one of your cells.
If you're as smart as you say you are,
will escape from here too.
He's the reason why
Company.
-Lord Glover, if you hear us.
Not supported.
No more.
Your brother is gone.
for your child to sleep."
The rest of your
We fight with the army
People despise her.
You are surrounded by enemies,
thousands of them.
Are you going to kill them alone?
to understand
It's the only joy I find
in this sadness.
These are not walkers
If it weren't for him,
Continuous!
It's a bad siege attempt.
Someone needs to teach them
to fulfill the oath
Need yes.
No.
It's not me. I'm just a mercenary.
You are an anointed knight.
There is a big difference.
Yes, passengers are not paid.
on other days, but no.
than a Lannister officer.
- It's like saying
- that I have a bigger penis...
That someone in the army
of the Immaculate.
I hope to command them all
It's still here for a reason.
You can be
I lost my right hand.
You promised me title
I am your killer.
After they're done with me,
- as a wife.
And it will have all three things.
-A Lannister always...
-Do not say that.
Do not say that.
Come out and fight us,
Black fish.
We have Lord Edmure.
Surrender the castle
- some bad years.
when the men of iron
Hand over the castle.
You think I won't do it,
You are old?
I slit your throat
it's not safe.
And where was it?
Running and hiding
like a coward.
Hand over the castle...
or I'll slit his throat.
Continue, then.
Cut your throat.
Lothar, right?
Mr Jaime.
We didn't know this was coming.
Why didn't you score?
a straight perimeter.
Permitiu que 8.000 homens
whose name is Stark.
I'm glad we're friends
otherwise they would be screwed now.
- Bathing and feeding
- Lord Edmure.
Walder.
Edmure is a prisoner
of House Frey.
He's the reason why
and does not put them into practice.
and served Stannis for years.
beat you...
unless you shut up,
but he kept talking.
What are you doing here?
I'm not bothered...
- Now you want
to get this castle back.
Could be skinned
Unless you want
take your place.
Sorry, Mr. Jaime.
Do what he says.
We don't have horses.
- under my command.
When the black fish appears
those walls...
you will see an army at the gates,
That's not what's there.
Make your men
dig trenches.
that the war is not between
- a cada 100 jardas.
I didn't know myself before.
in towers and trebuchets.
These are our towers...
As I said, the siege
is under my command.
that the war is not between
-They follow the Red God.
an intimate question?
I want a negotiation.
Negotiation or fight?
We must defend them.
You have one hand.
But you must go, grandma.
Kill them?
Welcome to Bear Island.
I will never leave my son.
- -Never.
You have the same name
What an Aunt Lyanna.
I don't want to fight anymore.
You will be too.
No more.
My mother was not beautiful nor did she have
any other kind of beauty.
She was a great warrior.
She died fighting
by his brother, Robb.
I served your uncle at the Castle
Black, Lady Lyanna.
He was also a great
warrior and a man of honor.
- I was your butler.
- I...
We've already said too much.
Why are you here?
Stannis Baratheon
I will hear her screaming
before marching
to Winterfell and be killed.
I saw the letter you wrote
when he asked for men. He said ...
I do not want anything.
That Bear Island only has...
our subordinates?
whose name is Stark.
Robb died,
but House Stark does not.
- I'm not going to make jokes
more than ever.
I came with my sister to ask
the alliance of House Mormont.
I understand that you are a snow
and Lady Sansa is a Bolton.
Or is she a Lannister?
I am your killer.
I did what I had to do
Hundreds will die.
they will come after you.
Drink it.
-Do not say that.
Anyway,
You don't want my ring.
- and we will kill
Ramsay Bolton cannot
take Winterfell, my lady.
It is our duty to stop it.
Even more so now that he
our brother Rickon...
by the Free People...
What you have to understand is that...
I'm responsible for Ilha dos
Bears and everyone who lives in it.
If we don't want to do
I pray your grandmother follows you.
for a war
Isn't that mine?
Please, my lady...
I understand how you feel.
I do not know him.
Sir...?
Davos, my lady,
of Seaworth House.
is to bring kindness to this world.
About my house. It's quite new.
Right, Mr. Davos
on other days, but no.
- How do you understand
- how I feel?
Never thought you'd find yourself
in this position.
and slit your wrists.
We will go to Meereen.
in a cell because of you.
who would be in this position.
I was the son of a fisherman,
So I was a drug dealer.
Now I talk to a lady
You are not in the right career.
in time of war.
are on the verge of collapse...
When my brother
It's our war.
You are sure.
- Your uncle,
- Lord Commander Mormont...
Maybe it's the Seven.
- your butler.
He chose Jon to be
his successor because he knew...
AND?
do what was right...
even if it meant
of your life.
Because Jeor Mormont
It's not what we expected.
that the war is not between
but House Stark is dead.
It is between the living and the dead.
And make no mistake, my lady...
the dead are coming.
And truth?
“The water passes through the stones,
in the Fist of the First Men.
I fought them in Durolar.
We both lost.
While the Boltons
There's Winterfell...
the North will be divided.
And a divided North will not have
chance against the Night King.
You want to protect your people.
He's the reason why
But there is no hiding.
the brute nature of a man.
and we have to fight together.
It is not enough.
com a Casa Stark há 1.000 anos.
We will not stop being loyal.
Thank you my lady.
- How many men
- We can wait?
You?
Sixty two?
We are not a big house,
We march for you.
And every man
from Bear Island...
Fight hard
of ten men from dry land.
If they have half
warrior and a man of honor.
the Boltons will be finished.
Regicide.
Black fish.
I think it's here...
to fulfill the oath
that my niece made.
without our illusions.
They are not with me.
Some of us still like it.
Do you want to go back to captivity?
And why are you here?
You know why I'm here.
This castle belongs
to Casa Frey. You invaded.
In the name of King Tommen,
I order you to surrender or...
Or will he kill Edmure?
I am your killer.
even death.
Company.
You promised me title
storming the castle.
After they're done with me,
Hundreds of mine.
With me. I shouldn't ask them.
- If you can cross
Gentlemen, please.
Congress requires no desire
I need you with me
- some bad years.
and we need to defeat them
if we want to continue
On my honor.
Your Honor?
Hard to find and more
it's not safe.
The war is over, sir.
Running and hiding
for a lost cause?
As long as you are alive,
It was smelly,
This is my house.
I'll keep a bowl
ready to die in it.
you coughed.
or starve us to death.
We have provisions
enough for two years.
Right, Mr. Davos
You clearly don't have any
But we still have a chance...
Why did you come to me?
Sieges are boring.
with you if we lose.
see who I deal with.
Well now you see me.
Yes, I saw it now.
I'm disappointed.
The answer is no.
-Lord Glover, if you hear us.
they will come after you.
We take back this castle
of the iron men.
since it's my last night
- Now you want
and your stupidity.
Could be skinned
just to talk.
It's our war.
-Roose Bolton...
Other northern houses
Will they fight for you?
House Mormont.
When the black fish appears
- We sent ravens
- for Casas Manderly...
I don't care about crows.
He was a soldier before.
let me join your army.
from Above, the future House Tyrell.
in this army?
Most of the strength
is made up of Savages.
So the rumors
-He can start again.
I didn't dare believe them.
I received it here
respect for his father.
- Now I would like
- go away.
Casa Glover will not abandon
your ancestral home...
You have one hand.
-Mister Glover!
-There is nothing more to say.
I would like to remind you that the Glover House
House Stark is compromised.
He swore to answer
when called.
when the time came,
House Stark for centuries.
We cried when we found out
of his father's death.
When my brother
He was the lord of this castle...
he fulfilled Robb's request
and acclaimed him King of the North.
And where was King Robb...
when the men of iron
Did they attack this castle?
When they put my
wife and children in prison...
and brutalized and killed
our subordinates?
Joining a slut
foreigner.
killing yourself
and those who followed him.
I served House Stark once,
but House Stark is dead.
Why did we have to come here?
Some of us still like it.
At least drink something.
I do not want anything.
Don't go far, love.
I'll find her now.
Nothing in the Iron Islands
such a donkey.
Are you no longer interested?
- I'm not going to make jokes
- about this.
I will never hurt you, little brother.
Don't you know that?
- Do you think Uncle Euron
- are you behind us?
Course is.
I am your killer.
Company.
It's a big world
I did what I had to do
Drink it.
even to the gods.
- I don't care what you want.
If you say.
Gentlemen, please.
We have Lord Edmure.
and we betray our own.
Ramsay Bolton cannot
Bad years?
while your mother screamed
cower like a dog.
Drink the damn beer.
Now listen to me.
difficult to navigate.
The real Theon Greyjoy,
This is not false.
Can you find it for me?
Drink it.
You escaped. Hearing this?
You ran away and will never return.
We will bring you justice.
If justice existed, it would be
hanging in Winterfell.
of Seaworth House.
We will take revenge. Drink it.
I put it in the cart, but it didn't happen.
If you're so devastated
There is no return...
take a knife
and slit your wrists.
End it.
and start helping people.
Theon, I need you.
too much to go back.
We will make a pact with
this Queen of Dragons.
And we will resume
the Iron Islands.
You are with me?
Are you really with me?
Now...
since it's my last night
on dry land...
I'm going to have sex with that one.
Stannis camped here
It's not just any war.
It's our war.
He was the commander
most experienced in Westeros.
Chose this place
his successor because he knew...
The mountains are
a natural fortification.
There's a stream there
for the horses.
- We're not staying here
- for a long time.
- There will be a storm
- any time.
Yes, the snows defeated
Stannis as much as the Boltons.
I will never forget.
now, while we can.
2.000 Selvagens...
200 Hornwoods, 143 Mazins...
62 Mormonts.
Why didn't they punish me?
Majesty.
some quarrelsome houses.
and be smart.
We will be the last
If you're as smart as you say you are,
trusted advisor now?
Porque ele garantiu 62 homens
de uma criança de 10 anos?
He's the reason why
I'm here talking to you...
and served Stannis for years.
Stannis who lost
Dark water...
who murdered his own
Brother, who doesn't have a head?
It is not enough.
We need more men.
There is no time.
If we went to the Castle
Let's pray?
We fight with the army
that we have.
Guys, it's not worth it
but we are proud.
We don't need to fight...
- -Who are you?
- -Hang on.
Yes, who are you?
He was a soldier before.
All my superiors
They thought I was brave.
Was not.
To mean,
I never ran away from a fight.
Just because I was scared that my
friends would see that he was scared.
He was just that, a coward...
who followed orders.
Lost.
Burn that village.
He is fine.
I'm your arsonist.
Steal the crops
of the farmer. I'm his thief.
Kill these young people
Or will he kill Edmure?
I am your killer.
Company.
shouting at us, saying...
So I was a drug dealer.
Drink it.
- If you can cross
Gentlemen, please.
Congress requires no desire
You too, come on.
- some bad years.
that boy...
while your mother screamed
and my friends held her.
That night...
You think I won't do it,
The shame was so heavy
that I couldn't eat...
I could not sleep.
All I could do was look
to that dark sky...
and hear that mother screaming
your child's name.
I will hear her screaming
before marching
I can't bring
that boy back.
All I can do
with the time left...
is to bring kindness to this world.
- That's all we can
- it does, doesn't it?
Nothing in the Iron Islands
stop stealing...
stop killing people...
and start helping people.
It's never late
too much to go back.
There is nothing to do
with answers to your prayers.
the Iron Islands.
- to do with the gods.
After they're done with me,
Learning that they have to respond
your own prayers.
and your stupidity.
How can we help?
It is not enough.
We are talking about life.
You?
Protecting the people.
I'm disappointed.
- They are protecting us
Do what he says.
by the Free People...
We don't have horses.
It's your brother?
We don't have steel.
those walls...
Protecting people makes people hungry.
you will see an army at the gates,
You can stay
for dinner...
but we have hungry mouths here.
Protect yourselves.
Are you sure they will come?
and full of horrors.
"May the Seven save you, friends."
I'm a damn cult.
What should I say?
They don't believe in their
Seven. They are from the Brotherhood.
-They follow the Red God.
-Yes, everyone is welcome here.
We have nothing for them.
Clear. They have food, steel,
even if they say no.
And you have women.
What do you want to do?
Fight them?
Kill them?
I didn't dare believe them.
Find comfort
Yes, you.
I don't want to fight anymore.
My mother was not beautiful nor did she have
Violence is a disease.
You can't cure a disease
spreading to more people.
Can't be cured by dying
hers too.
You've worked enough
for today. Come have dinner.
It will be cold tonight.
This is my house.
I'll keep a bowl
of stew for you.
I think I have beer
warrior and a man of honor.
He is not a liar.
Talk about the Iron Fleet in the Bay
of Slaves. And I believe him.
You don't know the things I've done.
those crazy people.
You are a Westerosi.
Why do you care?
I want to go home.
You?
will escape from here too.
-Where did you steal this from?
-Why do you care?
We will leave in two days.
There will be a hammock on the deck.
I want a cabin.
And we will leave at dawn.
Until then.
Good girl.